Guide to the Multicultural Student Services Center records, 1969-2016 RG0056
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Multicultural Student Services Center, 1969-1993; 1980-1993; RG0056 Series 1
  - Miller, Kenneth Eric, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 60)
  - EOP Spring 1984 Housing Forms, 1984 February 14; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 61)
  - Other University Minority Programs, 1983-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 62)
  - Nealon, Daniel McManus, 1984 May 4; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 63)
  - O'Dell, Gina Nicole, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 64)
  - Patmios, Georgeanne Elaine, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 65)
  - Prahinski, John R., 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 66)
  - Prather, Marcel M., 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 67)
  - Robins, Gerald Louis, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 68)
  - Rollins, Prentis Allen, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 69)
  - Sanders, Howard L., 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 70)
  - Smith, Quintin A., 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 71)
  - Stewart, Unita S., 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 72)
  - Van Flandern, Constance, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 73)
  - Willging, Patrick Aloysius, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 74)
  - Wilson, Teri S., 1984 April 15; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 75)
  - Winder, Karen, 1984 May 14; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 76)
  - Wong, Lik, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 77)
  - Wood, Stephen, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 78)
  - Yee, Mo, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 79)
  - Manago, Chiquita (Transfer), 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 80)
  - Alexander, Mark Bernard, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 81)
  - Black, Lasonja A., 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 82)
  - Boose, Tracee Danielle, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 83)
  - Boova, Nancy Ann, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 84)
  - Branson, Caroline Joy, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 85)
  - Budway, Vera Maria, 1984 February 6; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 86)
  - Burford, Lisa C., 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 87)
  - Carleton, Walter G., 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 88)
  - Connor, Chelo D., 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 89)
  - Currie, Ulysses Michael, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 90)
  - DePaul, Maria, 1984 June 20; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 91)
  - Franicis, Fitzroy Kensworth, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 92)
  - Freeman, Monica, 1984 June 21; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 93)
  - Frizzell, Antionette Cherie, 1984 June 4; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 94)
  - EOP Program Statistics and Information, 1970-1979; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 95)
  - Stockton, Julie, 1982; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 96)
  - EOP Information, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 97)
  - Hunt, William (Box 11A, Folder 1)
    - Foster, Leo (Box 11A, Folder 2)
    - Hester, Sheila (Box 11A, Folder 3)
    - Bell, Gerald (Box 11A, Folder 4)
    - Dickinson, Arnisha (Box 11A, Folder 5)
    - Parker, Phyllis (Box 11A, Folder 6)
    - Brice, Maria (Box 11A, Folder 7)
    - Hagan, Elizabeth (Box 11A, Folder 8)
    - Ivey, Gloria (Box 11A, Folder 9)
    - Minor, Sharon (Box 11A, Folder 10)
    - Worthy, Jacqueline (Box 11A, Folder 11)
    - Gamble, James (Box 11A, Folder 12)
    - Isaacs, Lisa (Box 11A, Folder 13)
    - Jones, Timothy (Box 11A, Folder 14)
    - Johnson, Cheryl (Box 11A, Folder 15)
    - Lee, Michael (Box 11A, Folder 16)
    - Lee, Rose (Box 11A, Folder 17)
    - Lewis, Latonia (Box 11A, Folder 18)
    - Martinez, Ana (Box 11A, Folder 19)
    - Miller, Kenneth (Box 11A, Folder 20)
    - EOP (Box 11A, Folder 21)
    - Nealon, Daniel (Box 11A, Folder 22)
    - Prather, Marcel [1/2] (Box 11A, Folder 23)
    - Prather, Marcel [2/2] (Box 11A, Folder 24)
    - SRNs, 04/1978 (Box 11A, Folder 25)
  - SRNs, 1978-April; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11B, Folder 1)
  - Self-Help References, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11B, Folder 2)
  - EOP Conference, 1970 September 11; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11B, Folder 3)
  - Southwest Texas State University, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11B, Folder 4)
  - EOP Tutorial Directory, 1979-1980, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11B, Folder 5)
  - Policies for the EOP, 1970 September 29; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11B, Folder 6)
  - The Money Manual, 2nd Edition Revised, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11B, Folder 7)
  - EOP: A Description of Goals and Objectives, 1971 June 4; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11B, Folder 8)
  - The GWU Student Organization Register 1977, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11B, Folder 9)
  - Criteria for EOP Grant Recision, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11B, Folder 10)
  - The Constitution of the GWU Program Board, 1975-January; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11B, Folder 11)
  - Affirmative Action Plan for The Handicapped (AAPH), 1979 October 22; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11B, Folder 12)
  - Current Issues in Higher Education, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11B, Folder 13)
  - GWU Organization Roster 1981-82, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11B, Folder 14)
  - The College Student With a Disability: A Faculty Handbook, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11B, Folder 15)
  - EOP Tutorial Directory, 1983-1984, 1983-September; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11B, Folder 16)
  - Washington Area Library Guide, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11B, Folder 17)
  - EOP Quick Reference Guide to Academic Procedures at GWU, Summer 1986, RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11B, Folder 18)
  - EOP Conference, 1970 September 11; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11B, Folder 19)
  - Handbook for the EOP, 1977 November; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11B, Folder 20)
  - EOP Student Data, Summer 1978-1979, 1979 June; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11B, Folder 21)
  - Howard University/National Medical Fellowships Workshop on Informed Decision Making, Financial Planning, and Management, 1985 March 13; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11B, Folder 22)
  - EOP Annual Reports, 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 1)
  - Academic Performance, 1986-1987; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 2)
  - EOP Annual Reports, 1987-1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 3)
  - EOP Students Performance Records (Blank), undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 4)
  - Prep Schedule Forms (Blank), undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 5)
  - Study Skills Questionaire (blank), undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 6)
  - Arrington, Tina, 1989-1992; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 7)
  - Anderson, Marsha Louise, 1987-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 8)
  - Atencia, Saul, 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 9)
  - Atkinson, Sophia, 1989 February 22; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 10)
  - Allen, Ralph Jr., 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 11)
  - Allen, William Jr., 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 12)
  - Anderson, Marsha, 1987-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 13)
  - Ali Alyassa Ali, Mohamed, 1987-1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 14)
  - Akinduro-Ali, Amira, 1987-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 15)
  - Afeta, Gifty, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 16)
  - Adams, Silvia, 1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 17)
  - Archer, Adrienne, 1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 18)
  - Ayllon, Rita, 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 19)
  - Beale, Tresa L. (Fall 1989 Admit), 1989 April 28; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 20)
  - Benn, Samuel, 1987-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 21)
  - Benn, Karen, 1985-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 22)
  - Bonds, Lillian, 1989 May 18; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 23)
  - Borden, Rosemary, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 24)
  - Bowes, Fenton, 1984-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 25)
  - Balthrop, Milinda-Jo, 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 26)
  - Bakaji, Rahaf, 1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 27)
  - Balthrop, Milinda-Jo, 1987-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 28)
  - Banks, Regina, 1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 29)
  - Barbour, Jennifer, 1986-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 30)
  - Barnum, Devaughn, 1987-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 31)
  - Brock, Tawana (Admit Fall 1991), RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 32)
  - Browne, Danna M. (Fall 1989 admit), RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 33)
  - Browning, Wilbur Jr., 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 34)
  - Bradley, Arthur Richon, 1984-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 35)
  - Brooks, Jason D., 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 36)
  - Bruce, Jr Arney, 1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 37)
  - Burton, Juliet R. (Fall 1989 Admit), RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 38)
  - Burden, Rodney, 1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 39)
  - Burton, June, 1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 40)
  - Burton, Stephanie, 1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 41)
  - Burgess, Latonya, 1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 42)
  - Baskin, Roger Sadannand, 1986-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 43)
  - Boyce, Tyra, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 44)
  - Butler, Marie (Fall 1989 Admit), RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 45)
  - Byrd, Sandra M., 1984-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 46)
  - Cacho, Bonita, 1981-1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 47)
  - Campbell, Andrew, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 48)
  - Campbell, Angelica, 1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 49)
  - Campbell, Peer, 1987-1992; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 50)
  - Campbell, Sabrina, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 51)
  - Capps, Roy, 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 52)
  - Carter, Richard, 1990-1993; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 53)
  - Boyd, Darryl, 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 54)
  - Carroll, Lisa (Fall 1989 admit), 1989 April 28; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 55)
  - Brown, Shelly, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 56)
  - Cisneros, Marco [1/2], 1981-1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 57)
  - Cisneros, Marco [2/2], 1981-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 58)
  - Coble, Sheila, 1987; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 59)
  - Tanya Coble Summer 1986, 1986-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 60)
  - Cullen, Devon [1/2], 1990 July 12; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 61)
  - Cullen, Devon [2/2], 1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 62)
  - Student Tests Address Update Info [empty], undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 63)
  - Ditoes 1975-76 [empty], undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 64)
  - Pot Pourri [empty], undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 65)
  - Grant Recision Policy [empty], undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 66)
  - Grade Sheets [empty], undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 67)
  - In-Service [empty], undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 68)
  - Grade Sheets [empty], undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 69)
  - Grade Sheets [empty], undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 70)
  - Graduate Student Letters, 1977 January 1; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 71)
  - The Herald (Vol. 1, No. 2), 1977 November; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 72)
  - EOP Students Enrolled in SGBA School, 1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 73)
  - Semester Records Forms (Blank), undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 74)
  - EOP Information Pamphlets, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 75)
  - EOP Tutorial Directory, 1980-1981, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 76)
  - Grant Recision, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 77)
  - Student Paraprofessionals Addressing Needs (SPAN), 1978 September; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 78)
  - 1977-1978 DCCES Members, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 79)
  - Division of Student Affairs "Highlights": Who's New-What's New, 1978 September 19; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 80)
  - EOP Observes 10th Anniversary, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 81)
  - Project Open: Opportunity Project for Education Now, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 82)
  - District of Columbia High Schools, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 83)
  - "SAVE" - Printing, 1979-1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 84)
  - Non-EOP Form Letter [Admissions Form Letters], 1981; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 85)
  - EOP Mailings (Forms), 1983 December 1; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 86)
  - Bereavement Leave Form [Julia J. Stockton], 1981 December; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 87)
  - EOP Monthly Report, 1981 October; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 88)
  - Staff Meeting Prep, 1981; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 89)
  - Stockton, Julia Leave Record Cards, 1976-1978; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 90)
  - EOP Graduation, 1969-1973; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 91)
  - 1981-82 Peer Counselor/Student List, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 92)
  - Spring 1980 Registration: Letter Forms [empty], undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 93)
  - EOP Performance Records, 1982-1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 94)
  - E.O.P. Prep, 1982; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 95)
  - EOP Objectives & Goals, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 96)
  - Applicant Credentials record (blank forms), undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 97)
  - Guide to University Expenses for 1982-1983, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 98)
  - EOP Finanical Aid Recipients, 1973 April; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 99)
  - Notes on Course Books, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 100)
  - Course Information (Schedule and Books), 1982-1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 101)
  - Buffet Diner (June 30, 1982), 1982 June 29; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 102)
  - Handbook for the EOP, 1977 November; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 103)
  - Rationale for EOP Grant Recision Policy, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 104)
  - 1980-81 EOP Students, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 105)
  - Minority Disparity on College Campuses, 1977 December; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 106)
  - Moving of University Stores Memo, 1982 October 6; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 107)
  - HI/SCIP 1983 Spring Semester Registration, 1982 November 2; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 108)
  - Notes on Student's Applicaion Materials, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 109)
  - EOP 1981-82 Annual Report, 1982 September; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 110)
  - 1981-1982 EOP Students, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 111)
  - 1981 Spring Graduates, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 112)
  - Students Entering Summer 1982, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 113)
  - 1982 PREP and HI/SCIP Students, 1982 September; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 114)
  - Student Files, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12A, Folder 115)
  - Anderson, Marsha (Box 12A, Folder 1)
    - Autencio, Saul (Box 12A, Folder 2)
    - Allen, Ralph (Box 12A, Folder 3)
    - Ali, Mohamed (Box 12A, Folder 4)
    - Archer, Adrienne (Box 12A, Folder 5)
    - Ayllon, Rita (Box 12A, Folder 6)
    - Bede, Tresa, 1989 (Box 12A, Folder 7)
    - Benn, Karen (Box 12A, Folder 8)
    - Bonds, Lillian (Box 12A, Folder 9)
    - Bowers, Fenton (Box 12A, Folder 10)
    - Bakjaji, Rahaf (Box 12A, Folder 11)
    - Banks, Regina (Box 12A, Folder 12)
    - Barber, Jennifer (Box 12A, Folder 13)
    - Barnun, D. (Box 12A, Folder 14)
    - Brock (Box 12A, Folder 15)
    - Brown, D. (Box 12A, Folder 16)
    - Browning Jr., Wilbur (Box 12A, Folder 17)
    - Bruce, Abney Jr. (Box 12A, Folder 18)
    - Burden, Rodney (Box 12A, Folder 19)
    - Burton, June (Box 12A, Folder 20)
    - Burton, Patrick (Box 12A, Folder 21)
    - Burgess, Latonya (Box 12A, Folder 22)
    - Butler, Marie (Box 12A, Folder 23)
    - Byrd, Sandra (Box 12A, Folder 24)
    - Student files, 1988-1989 (Box 12A, Folder 25)
    - HISCIP students, 1979 (Box 12A, Folder 26)
  - Akus, Gregory Fall 1979 HI/SCIP, 1979-1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 1)
  - Borders, Chaye Fall 1979 HI/SCIP, 1979-1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 2)
  - Brown, Felicia Summer 1979 HI/SCIP, 1979-1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 3)
  - Brown, Jerome Summer 1979 HI/SCIP, 1979-1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 4)
  - Butler, Antoinette Summer 1979 HI/SCIP, 1979-1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 5)
  - Fletcher, Michael Fall1979 HI/SCIP, 1979-1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 6)
  - Graves, Phyllis (Enter Sp 1980) HI/SCIP, 1979-1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 7)
  - Harrod, Larry (Enter Sp 1980) HI/SCIP, 1979-1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 8)
  - Holt, Gregory (Fall 1979) HI/SCIP, 1979-1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 9)
  - Kennedy, Jacquelyn Summer 1979 HI/SCIP, 1979-1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 10)
  - Landfair, Keith Summer 1979 HI/SCIP, 1979-1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 11)
  - Montague, Monica (Summer 1979) HI/SCIP, 1979-1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 12)
  - Nixon, Deidra Fall 1979 HI/SCIP, 1979-1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 13)
  - Reynolds, Rebecca Fall 1979 HI/SCIP, 1979-1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 14)
  - West, Geoffry (Enter Sp 1980) HI/SCIP, 1979-1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 15)
  - Williams, Ken (Enter Sp 1980), 1979-1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 16)
  - Student Information, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 17)
  - HI/SCIP Students Fall 1983, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 18)
  - Misc. Meeting Notes, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 19)
  - Academic Guide for Entering Students, 1980-April; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 20)
  - Closing Schedule: 1982-83 Fiscal Year Accounts, 1983 May 4; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 21)
  - 1980-1983 EOP Summer School Request Forms, 1981-1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 22)
  - International Services Newsletter (Vol. 9, no. 2), 1981 March; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 23)
  - Administrative Procedures and Program Reports, Summary of Needs, 1981 December 7; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 24)
  - The Chronicle of Higher Education (vol. 20, no. 13), 1980 May 27; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 25)
  - QYX: The Intelligent Typewriter Infomation, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 26)
  - Criteria for EOP Grant Recision, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 27)
  - EOP Interview Request Lette (Blank), undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 28)
  - EOP Handbook Correspondence, 1977 November 30; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 29)
  - Application for Admission: Georgetown/District of Columbia Medical-Dental Health Caeers Programs, 1979; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 30)
  - Reception Honoring the 1981 EOP Spring and Summe Graduates Correspondence, 1981 April 24; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 31)
  - EOP Policy Admendments, 1978 December 13; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 32)
  - First Thursdays during 1982-83, 1982 July 29; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 33)
  - Graduate Fellowship Information Center Informaion, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 34)
  - EOP Students Performance Record (Blank Forms), undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 35)
  - Mailing Rates and Helpful Hints, 1981-1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 36)
  - HI/SCIP Program Information, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 37)
  - Contents of File Drawer #4 (Forms), undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 38)
  - EOP Handwritten Notes, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 39)
  - Division Publication, 1982 September 8; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 40)
  - EOP Preliminary Interview Sheet, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 41)
  - National Association of Black Social Workers, Inc.: 15th Annual Conference, April 11-17, 1983, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 42)
  - It's Your Turn to Play! A Creative Alternative to Burn Out with Ed Lilley, 1983 April 30; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 43)
  - SAVE-for printed copies, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 12B, Folder 44)
  - Men's Basketball Team "Open House", October 29, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Brochure, 1982-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Day, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Open House, 1979-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Handbook for the Education Opportunity Program, November 1977; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - "Education Opportunity Program for District of Columbia Students" Brochure, 1988-1989; RG0056 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Newletter, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Newsletter: Distributed Editions, 1982-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    Dean Hanson
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Newsletter with Corrections by Dean Hanson, January 6, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Washington Area Library Guide, 1976-1981; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Special Activities, 1981-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Senate Meeting Minutes, FY 1987-1988 [1/2], RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Senate Meeting Minutes, FY 1987-1988 [2/2], RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Special Activities Forms and Correspondence, 1978-1979; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Students Performance Records, Academic Year 1985-1986, RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Housing, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Student Financial Aid, Selected Report, 1987-1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Pot Luck Holiday Party, December 21, 1987; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Instructions for Hold 'n Fold Copyholder Model HF-1, 1987; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Proposal to the GTE Corporation for a "Focus" Grant, 1986-1987; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Recommendations Regarding a University Hazing Policy, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - The Inner City Student Assistance Fund, 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Internship Correspondence, 1985-1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Materials Held for Annual Reports, 1987-1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    Materials include Hatchet newspapers, MSSC activity fliers, and GW Reports.
  - The Educational Opportunity Report Blank Interview Forms, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Blank HI/SCIP Interview Forms, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Marvin Center and the Student Activities Office (SAO) Consolidation Committee [1/2], March - April 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Marvin Center and the Student Activities Office (SAO) Consolidation Committee [2/2], March - April 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Annual Report and Related Materials, FY 1985-1986, RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Minority Student Initiatives, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - MSSC Related News Coverage, 1987-1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - The Education Opportunity Program Peer Counselor Training Workshop, 1981-1982; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Peer Counselor Job Description, May 6, 1981; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Department of Personnel Services Training Division Programs, 1980-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Pre-College Review and Enrichment Program (PREP), 1982-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Development and History, 1971-1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Academic Recommendations, 1983-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Summer Advance Registration Program (SARP) Participants, 1980-1982; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 39)